《玩具总动员2》
(伽玛象限  第四区域)
Buzz Lightyear mission log.
巴斯光年任务日志
All signs point to this planet as the location of Zurg's fortress,
所有的迹象都显示,这就是札克天王的星球
but there seems to be no sign of intelligent life anywhere.
但是却没有,智慧形生物的踪影
(太空骑警巴斯光年)
(札克天王监视器)
Come to me, my prey.
自投罗网吧,我的猎物
(札克天王能量库)
To infinity and beyond!
飞向宇宙…浩瀚无垠
(札克天王能量库)
So, we meet again, Buzz Lightyear, for the last time.
我们又见面了,巴斯光年,这次你死定了
Not today, Zurg!
你休想,札克
(游戏结束)
You almost had him.
不…不…,你差点就打败他
- I'm never gonna defeat Zurg! - Sure, you will, Rex...
- 我永远都赢不了札克 - 你会赢的,抱抱龙
In fact, you're a better Buzz than I am.
你当巴斯比我还要厉害
But look at my little arms!
我的手太短了
I can't press the "fire" button and jump at the same time!
我不能同时按发射和跳跃的按键
Where is it? Where is it?
在哪儿?
- Woody? - Huh?
- 胡迪 - 嗯?
Hang on, cowboy!
别慌,牛仔
- Woody, are you all right? - Yeah.
- 你没事吧? - 是的
Yeah, I'm fine, Buzz. OK. Here's your list of things to do while I'm gone.
我没事啦,巴斯,我不在的时候别忘了这些事
Batteries need to be changed.
记得要换电池
Toys in the bottom of the chest need to be rotated.
让柜底的玩具出来透透气
And make sure everyone attends Mr. Spell's seminar...
大家都要上拼字先生的课
on what to do if you or a part of you is swallowed.
“玩具被吞食该如何应变”
OK? OK. Good. OK.
好吗?很好
Woody, you haven't found your hat yet, have you?
你还没找到帽子,对吧?
And Andy's leaving for cowboy camp any minute,
对,安弟要参加牛仔营
and I can't find it anywhere!
我却找不到牛仔帽
Don't worry, Woody. In just a few hours,
别担心,再过几个钟头
you'll be sitting around a campfire with Andy making delicious, hot "sch'moes."
你就能跟安弟坐在营火旁,一起烤香喷喷的马铃薯
- They're called s'mores, Buzz. - Right. Right. Of course.
- 是蕃薯啦,巴斯 - 没错,好吧
Has anyone found Woody's hat yet?
谁找到胡迪的帽子吗?
Keep looking, men. Dig deeper! Negatory. Still searching.
弟兄们,继续找报告,我们还在找
The lawn gnome next door says it's not in the yard, but he'll keep lookin'.
前院小矮人说不在院子里,但是他会继续找
It's not in Molly's room. We've looked everywhere.
我们到处都找过了,不在茉莉房间
- I found it. - You found my hat?
- 我找到了 - 你找到我的帽子?
Your hat? No. The missus lost her earring.
你的帽子?不是啦,我老婆丢了耳环
- My little sweet potato! - You found it!
- 我的亲亲蛋头太太 - 你找到了
It's so nice...
家里有个
to have a big, strong spud around the house.
强壮的蛋头老公真好
That's just great.
这下可好了
This'll be the first year I miss cowboy camp, all because of my stupid hat!
我去不成牛仔营,都是因为一顶蠢帽子
- Woody, look under your boot. - Don't be silly.
- 胡迪,看看你的靴底 - 别傻了
- My hat is not under my boot. - Would you just look?
- 帽子不在那儿 - 你看看嘛
No hat. Just the word "Andy".
瞧,没有帽子,只有“安弟”这两个字
And the boy who wrote that
不管你有没有帽子
would take you to camp with or without your hat.
他还是会带你去牛仔营
I'm sorry, Bo.
对不起,宝贝
It's just that I've been lookin' forward to this all year.
只是我等了一整年
It's my one time with just me and Andy.
才能单独跟安弟相处
You're cute when you care.
你这样好可爱哦
- Bo, not in front of Buzz. - Let him look.
- 别在巴斯面前这样嘛 - 他爱看就看
Miss Peep, your sheep!
宝贝小姐,你的绵羊
This is Al from Al's Toy Barn
我是艾而玩具城的艾而
and I'm sittin' on good deals.
这儿有便宜货
I think I'm feeling a deal hatching right now.
好东西正要破卵而出
Let's see what we got. We got boats for a buck Beanies for a buck...
让我看看有什么,我有一块钱的玩具船、豆娃娃
- Turn it off! Someone's gonna hear! - Which one is off?
- 快关掉,有人会听到 - 怎么关呀?
Buck-buck-buck! And that's cheap-cheap-cheap! So hurry on down...
价钱低得咕咕叫
For cryin' out loud, it's this one.
是这个按钮
- I despise that chicken. - Fellas! Fellas!
- 我最恨那只鸡 - 大伙儿
OK, I got some good news, and I got some bad news.
我有好消息跟坏消息
What news?
快说吧,什么消息?
The good news is I found your hat, Woody.
好消息是我找到你的帽子
My hat! Slink, thank you. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
我的帽子,弹簧狗,谢谢你…
- Where'd you find it? - Well, that's the bad news.
- 你在哪儿找到的? - 这就是坏消息
It's Buster!
是小狗巴斯特
Canine alert! Man your battle stations!
恶犬来袭!全面备战!
Let's move, move, move!
快行动!
Woody! Hide! Quick!
胡迪,快躲起来
OK, OK, OK. OK, OK! You found me!
好啦…好啦…你找到我了
Buster, all right. Hey, how did he do, Hamm?
夠了,巴斯特,火腿,它的表现如何?
- Looks like a new record. - OK, boy. Sit.
- 它又刷新纪录 - 乖,狗狗,坐下
Reach for the sky.
把手举起来
Gotcha!
你死了
Great job, boy.
好棒哦,狗狗
Who's gonna miss me while I'm gone, huh?
我走了谁会想我?
Who's gonna miss me?
谁会想我?
谁会想我呀?
Andy, you got all your stuff?
安弟,你的袋子呢?
Have a good weekend, everybody. I'll see you Sunday night.
大伙儿周末愉快,礼拜天见
It's in my room.
在我的房间
Stick 'em up.
手举起来
I guess we'll work on that later.
我改天再教你吧
Hey, Woody. Ready to go to cowboy camp?
胡迪,准备去牛仔营啰
Andy, honey, come on. Five minutes, and we're leavin'.
安弟,快点,五分钟后出发
Five minutes.
五分钟
Help, help! Somebody help me!
救命啊!谁来救我?
Let her go, evil Dr. Pork Chop!
邪恶的猪排博士,放开她
Never!
不行
You must choose, Sheriff Woody. How shall she die?
你得选择,胡迪警长,你要她怎么死?
Shark, or death by monkeys?
鲨鱼?还是被猴子吃掉?
Choose!
快选择吧
I choose Buzz Lightyear!
我选择巴斯光年
(星际总部)
What? That's not a choice!
那可不行
To infinity and beyond!
飞向宇宙…浩瀚无垠
- I'll save you, Miss Peep. - My hero.
- 我来救你,宝贝小姐 - 我的大英雄
- Thanks, Buzz. - No problem, buddy.
- 谢了,巴斯 - 不客气,兄弟
You should never tangle with the unstoppable duo
千万别惹上所向无敌的…
of Woody and Buzz Lightyear!
…胡迪和巴斯光年
Oh, no.
糟了
Andy, let's go! Molly's already in her car seat.
安弟,走了,妹妹都上车了
- But, Mom, Woody's arm ripped. - Oh, no.
- 妈咪,胡迪的手被扯破了 - 糟糕
- Maybe we can fix. Him on the way. - No, just leave him.
- 也许可以在路上补好 - 不要,别带去吧
I'm sorry, honey, but you know toys don't last forever.
别难过,乖乖,玩具没有永远不坏的
(三星级牛仔营)
- What happened? - Woody's been shelved.
- 怎么回事? - 胡迪被放到架子上
Andy!
安弟
(小狗岛)
(超大卡车)
- Woody? - Woody? Honey, are you OK?
- 胡迪? - 胡迪,帅哥,你还好吧?
Ride 'em, cowboy!
咿呀,快骑吧,牛仔
He's back? Hey, everybody! Andy's back! He's back early from cowboy camp!
他回来了?他回来了,安弟从牛仔营提早回来了
Places, everybody! Andy's coming!
各就各位,安弟来了
Hey, Woody! Did you miss me?
胡迪,你想我吗?
Giddyap, giddyap, giddyap. Ride 'em, cowboy!
跑吧…马儿,快骑吧,牛仔
I forgot. You're broken.
我忘了,你坏了
I don't wanna play with you anymore.
我不要跟你玩了
(安弟)
No, Andy! No. No, Andy! No!
不,安弟,不!
Andy. Andy.
安弟,安弟
Bye, Woody.
永别了,胡迪
No! No! Andy!
安弟,别走!
Wheezy, is that you?
吱吱,是你吗?
- Hey, Woody. - What are you doing up here?
- 嗨,胡迪 - 你怎么会在这儿?
I thought Mom took you to get your squeaker fix. Ed months ago.
我以为妈咪,老早就把你修好了
- Andy was so upset. - Nah.
- 安弟很着急耶 - 没有
She just told him that to calm him down
她只是安慰安弟而已
and then put me on the shelf.
然后就把我放上来
- Why didn't you yell for help? - Well, I tried squeakin'.
- 你怎么不求救呢? - 我试着吱吱叫
But I'm still broken. No one could hear me.
可是没有用,没有人听得到
Besides, the dust aggravates my condition.
况且灰尘让我病得更重
What's the point in prolonging the inevitable?
反正我是无药可救了
We're all just one stitch away from here to there.
我们最后都会沦落到那儿的
Yard sale? Yard sale!
前院拍卖
Yard sale! Guys, wake up, wake up! There's a yard sale outside!
前院拍卖!大伙儿,醒醒,外面在拍卖
- Yard sale? - Sarge, emergency roll call!
- 前院拍卖? - 队长,紧急点名
Sir, yes, sir! Red alert!
是,长官,紧急状况
All civilians fall in position now! Single file! Let's move, move, move!
马上全体集合,排成一列,快点
- Hamm? - Here.
- 火腿 - 在这
- Potato Head, Mr. And Mrs? - Here.
- 蛋头先生、太太 - 在
Troikas. Check, check, check, check, check.
蛋包蛋,在在在在在
I hate yard sales!
我最讨厌大拍卖
Someone's coming!
有人来了
OK. Let's see what's up here.
好吧,让我看看有什么
(组合玩具)
Bye, Woody.
永别了,胡迪
Wheezy! Think, think, Woody. Think, think, think.
吱吱,快点,胡迪,快想办法
Hey. Here, boy. Here, Buster!
狗狗,我在上面
Up here!
这里
No...No...
不…不…
OK, boy. To the yard sale!
好了,快到前院
What's goin' on? He's nuts.
怎么回事?他秀逗了
His arm ain't that bad.
他的手没那么糟嘛
Don't do it, Woody! We love you!
别去找死,我们爱你
Careful on the steps, now.
下楼梯小心点
OK, boy. Let's go. And keep it casual.
走吧,狗狗,要装得若无其事
Not that casual.
不是装腔作势啦
Piggy bank coming through, coming through.
火腿大爷来也
- Is he out there? - There he is.
- 他在外面吗? - 他在那儿
(两毛五)
He's in the box!
他爬进箱子了
He's sellin' himself for 25 cents!
他只把自己标价两毛五
You're worth more than that.
胡迪,你没这么不值钱吧
Hold on. Hold on. He's got something.
等等,他找到什么
- It's Wheezy! - Wheezy?
- 是吱吱 - 吱吱?
Hey, it's not suicide. It's a rescue.
他不是自杀,他是去救人
Good boy, Buster. Hold still. There. There you go, pal.
乖狗狗,别乱动,来吧,好兄弟
- Bless you, Woody. - All right, now.
- 你真好,胡迪 - 好了
Back to Andy's room.
回安弟房间吧
Way to go, cowboy.
干得好,牛仔
- Golly bob howdy! - Woody, I'm slipping!
- 真是了不起 - 胡迪,我快掉下去了
Mommy... Mommy, look! Look at this!
妈咪,你看看
- Mommy, look! It's a cowboy dolly! - Hey, that's not her toy!
- 你看,是一个牛仔娃娃 - 胡迪不是她的玩具
What's that little gal think she's doin'?
那个小女孩想干嘛?
Mommy, Mommy, can we get it? Please? Mommy, please?
妈咪,卖啦,好不好?
You don't want that toy. It's broken.
乖乖,不要啦,它坏了
There's a snake in my boot.
我的靴子里有蛇
Original hand-painted face. Natural-dyed, blanket-stitched vest!
原版手工上漆,天然染色、锁边背心
Little rip. Fix. Able. If only you had your hand-stitched, polyvinyl...
有点破,能补救,希望有你的手缝尼龙布制…
A hat! I found him! I found him! I found him!
…牛仔帽,我找到了,我找到了
Buster! Quiet down!
巴斯特,安静
- Ex. Cuse me. Can I help you? - Yes.
- 抱歉,我能帮忙吗? - 当然能
You can help take his paws off my pal.
叫他别碰我的好友
I'll give you 50 cents for all this junk.
我出五毛钱卖这个破玩具
- Now, how did this get down here? - Hand her the sheriff.
- 这怎么会在这儿? - 乖乖的把警长…
Nice and easy.
…交给她
- Five dollars. - I'm sorry. It's an old family toy.
- 五块钱 - 抱歉,这是家里的玩具
Now just walk away.
乖乖给我走开
- Wait. - The other way.
- 等等 - 另外一边
- I'll give you 50 bucks for him. - Fifty bucks ain't bad.
- 我出五十块钱 - 五十元不少钱耶
- It's not for sale. - Everything's for sale.
- 我不卖 - 什么都能卖卖或交易
- Or trade. You like my watch? - Sorry.
- 喜欢我的表吗? - 抱歉
- He's safe. Way to go! - She showed him!
- 他得救了,安弟的妈咪万岁 - 棒呆了,她让他吃瘪
- Molly, don't touch that, sweetie. - Yeah. Go home, Mr. Fancy Car.
- 茉莉,别乱摸 - 滚回家吧,胖子
- Hold on. - What's up?
- 等等 - 什么事?
What is it, Buzz?
巴斯,怎么了?
What's happening?
发生什么事?
What's he doing?
他在干嘛?
I can't watch! Can someone cover my eyes?
我不敢看,矇住我的眼睛,好吗?
- He's stealin' Woody! - What? He can't take Woody.
- 他想要偷走胡迪 - 什么?
It's illegal.
那是犯法的
- Where's he going? - Do something.
- 他去哪儿? - 想想办法呀
Buzz!
巴斯
Get him, Buzz.
巴斯,阻止他
Where's the red jacket?
红色夹克在哪里?
(要卖请早)
(三郡车牌)
Why would someone steal Woody?
怎么会有人要偷走胡迪呢?
(儿童不宜进入)
(证物A)
All right. Let's review this one more time.
我们再回顾一次
At precisely 8:32-ish,
8时32分左右
Ex. Hibit A, Woody, was kidnapped.
证物A胡迪遭到绑架
Ex. Hibit B, a composite sketch of the kidnapper.
证物B绑匪的素描
- He didn't have a beard like that. - Fine. Etch, give him a shave.
- 他的胡子没那么长 - 好吧,画板,帮他刮胡子
The kidnapper was bigger than that.
绑匪比较胖
- Picky, picky, picky. - Let's just go straight to Ex. Hibit F.
- 你们真挑剔 - 直接跳到证物F
The kidnapper's vehicle.
绑匪的车子
Now, the vehicle fled the scene in this direction.
他从这方向逃离现场
Your eyes are in backwards. It went the other way.
你的眼睛装反了,是另一边啦
Hey. Put a cork in it.
别教训我,猪头
- How do you spell FBI? - My crime scene!
- FBI英文怎么拼呀? - 我的犯罪现场
Why don't you watch where you're going, Godspilla?
瞎眼龙,走路要看路,好吗?
- I didn't know there was a crime scene. - Ex. Cuse me. Ex. Cuse me.
- 我没看到犯罪现场 - 不好意思
A little quiet, please. Thank you.
请安静点,谢谢
Lazy toy brain.
懒骨头
- Lousy try Brian. - What are you doing, Buzz?
- 逊角色 - 巴斯,你在干嘛?
It's some sort of message encoded on that vehicle's I.D. Tag.
那辆车的车牌暗藏玄机
- Liz try bran. - It's just a license plate.
- 试试... - 车牌的字母没什么意义
- It's just a jumble of letters. - Yeah, and there are about
- 只是一堆乱七八糟的信件 - 没错,本郡总共有...
3.5 million registered cars in the tri-county area alone.
三百五十万辆汽车
Lou's thigh burn.
没用的软脚虾
This can't help. Let's leave Buzz to play with his toys.
没有用啦,让巴斯继续玩玩具吧
Toy. Toy. Toy. Hold on!
玩具…等等!
- Al's Toy Barn. - Al's Toy Barn!
- 艾而玩具城 - 艾而玩具城!
Etch, draw that man in a chicken suit.
画板,画出扮成公鸡的人
It's the chicken man!
就是那个公鸡人
That's our guy.
他就是嫌犯
I knew there was something I didn't like about that chicken.
我早就知道那只鸡有问题
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'll be right there.
好啦,我马上来
And we're gonna do this commercial in one take, do you hear me,
这次广告要一次搞定
because I am in the middle of something really important.
因为我正在办一件正事
You, my little cowboy friend, are gonna make me big buck-buck-bucks.
我的小牛仔朋友,你会让我发大猜…
Andy!
安弟
I can't believe I have to drive all the way to work on a Saturday.
我不敢相信,他们礼拜六竟然…
All the way to work!
…要我大老远开车跑去上班
(艾而玩具城)
What?
什么?
Hey! Stop! Horsy, stop! Stop! Sit, boy!
停!马儿,停!坐下来!
Stop it! Sit, I said!
我叫你坐!
It's you! It's you! It's you! It's you! It's you!
是你…是你…是你…
- It's really you! - What's me?
- 真的是你! - 是我
There's a snake in my boot.
我的靴子里有蛇
- It is you! - Please stop saying that.
- 就是你 - 请你别再说了
Prospector said someday you'd come.
老矿工就说有一天你会来
Sweet mother of Abraham Lincoln!
乖乖老天爷
The Prospector! He'll wanna meet ya!
老矿工一定很想见你
Say "hello" to the Prospector!
过来跟老矿工问好
(邋遢矿工彼得)
- It... It's a box... - He's mint in the box...
- 这是个盒子 - 他是全新的
Never been opened.
没有拆封过
Turn me around, Bullseye, so I can see.
红心,把我转过来,让我看看
(胡迪牛仔秀系列玩具)
Why, the prodigal son has returned.
浪子终于回头了
It's you! It's you!
是你,你来了
You're here! It's you! It's you! It's you!
是你…是你…
OK. I'm officially freaked-out now.
我真的被吓坏了
We've waited countless years for this day.
我们等了多少年,才等到这一天
- It's good to see you, Woody. - Listen. I don't know wh...
- 很高兴见到你,胡迪 - 听好,我不知道…
- Hey, how do you know my name? - Everyone knows your name, Wood-y.
- 你怎么知道我的名字? - 你的名字家喻户晓,胡迪
Why, you don't know who you are, do you? Bullseye?
你不记得自己是谁吗?红心
(胡迪牛仔秀)
That's me.
那是我耶
(牛仔牌玉米脆片  胡迪牛仔秀)
(牛仔牌玉米脆片)
(胡迪牛仔秀)
Wow.
哇赛
(时代杂志  生活杂志)
Holy cow.
老天爷
Cowboy Crunchies
牛仔牌玉米脆片
the cereal that's sugar-frosted and dipped in chocolate
唯一的巧克力口味壳类早餐
proudly presents:
热情赞助
Woody's Roundup Come on it's time to play
胡迪牛仔秀,大家一起玩
There's Jessie the yodeling cowgirl
那是翠丝,唱歌女牛仔
Look it! That's me!
瞧,那是我
- Bullseye he's Woody's horse - He's a smart one
- 红心,胡迪的好马儿 - 他真聪明
- Pete the old Prospector - Has anyone seen my pick?
- 邋遢矿工彼得 - 我的丁字鎚呢?
And the man himself Of course it's time for Sheriff Woody
当然还有男主角他本人
He's the very best
胡迪警长他最行
He's the rootin'-est tootin'-est cowboy
他是西部
In the wild wild west
最棒最酷最炫的警长
Woody's Roundup
胡迪牛仔秀
(选台  音量)
I can't find it! It doesn't seem to be on any of these stations.
我找不到,每一台都找不到
- Keep looking. - You're going too slow.
- 继续找 - 你转得太慢了
Let me take the wheel.
让我来
It's too fast.
太快了
- How can you even tell what's on? - I can tell.
- 你怎么看得到? - 我看得到
Stop! Back, back, back!
转回去,回去
Too late. I'm in the 40s. Got to go 'round the horn. It's faster.
太晚了,转过头了,我要从头开始
- Back, back! Stop! - And look for the giant chicken!
- 对了 - 找到大公鸡就没错
Now, Etch!
画板,快画吧
That's where I need to go.
我一定要去这里
You can't go, Buzz. You'll never make it there.
不行,巴斯,你办不到的
Woody once risked his life to save me.
上次胡迪冒险救我
I couldn't call myself his friend if I weren't willing to do the same.
这次我不去救他,就不配当他的朋友
So who's with me?
谁要跟来?
I'm packing you an extra pair of shoes and your angry eyes just in case.
我替你多装一双鞋,还有愤怒的双眼,以防万一
This is for Woody when you find him.
我要你找到胡迪,替我亲他一下
All right,
好吧,可是我亲他
but I don't think it'll mean the same coming from me.
跟你亲他的意义很不同
Mr. Buzz Lightyear, you just gotta save my pal Woody.
巴斯光年先生,你一定要把胡迪救出来
I'll do my best, son.
我会尽力而为,吱吱
OK, fellas. Let's roll.
好了,大伙儿,出发吧
Geronimo!
我跳了
You'd think with all my video game ex. Perience,
我有这么多打电玩的经验
I'd be feeling more prepared.
所以应该是难不倒我
The idea is to let go.
重点是…你得放手
We'll be back before Andy gets home.
我们会赶在安弟之前回来
Don't talk to any toy you don't know!
别随便跟陌生玩具说话
To Al's Toy Barn and beyond!
飞向艾而玩具城
They don't call this
老矿工
the old abandoned mine for nothin' Prospector.
这座废弃矿坑真是可怕
I reckon we oughta get outta here.
我们最好赶紧出去
Where's my gold? Hold on. I'll light me a candle.
我的黄金呢?等等,我来点蜡烛
This sure is a fast-burnin' wick.
这根蜡烛烧得好快
Blast us to smithereens! That there's dynamite!
这是炸药,我们完蛋了
- Holy tarnation! - I'll call for help.
- 我的妈呀 - 让我来求救
Hey critters go get Sheriff Woody. Now scurry!
小动物,去找胡迪警长,快去
Good job Bullseye.
真好,红心
I reckon the new schoolhouse is finally done.
新的学校终于盖好了
What's that?
什么?
Jessie and Prospector are trapped in the old abandoned mine
翠丝和老矿工,被困在废弃矿坑
and Prospectorjust lit a stick of dynamite thinkin' it was a candle
老矿工误触炸药
and now they're about to be blown to smithereens?
他们就快要被炸成碎片?
Ride like the wind Bullseye!
红心,快马加鞭吧
You're fannin' the flames Jessie! It takes brains to put out that fire.
别煽风点火,翠丝,你得用头脑才能熄灭炸药
My biscuits are burnin'!
我的屁股着火了
(大峡谷)
Will Woody and Bullseye land to safety?
胡迪跟红心能跃过大峡谷吗?
Can they reach Jessie and Stinky Pete in time?
他们能及时救出,翠丝跟老矿工彼得吗?
Tune in net week for the eciting conclusion: "Woody's Finest Hour."
下周同一时间记得收看《胡迪冒险记》大结局
All right! All right! Next tape!
棒呆了,下一集
Hey, wait. What happened? What happens next?
等等,接下来怎么样?
- Come on! Let's see the next episode! - That's it.
- 我要看大结局 - 没有了
What?
什么?
The show was canceled after that.
后来节目被迫停播
Wait, wait, wait. What about the gold mine
慢着,那座废弃矿坑
and the cute little critters and the dynamite?
可爱的小动物跟炸药呢?
That was a great show! I mean, why cancel it?
这么精采的节目,怎么会被停播呢?
Two words: Sput-nik.
三个字：太空人
Once the astronauts went up, children only wanted to play with space toys.
太空人一登陆月球,小孩子只想玩太空玩具
I know how that feels. But still, my own show.
我知道那种感觉,我有自己的节目耶
- I mean, look at all this stuff! - Didn't you know?
- 你们看看这些玩意 - 你不知道吗?
Why, you're valuable property!
你是热门的抢手货耶
I wish the guys could see this. Hey-howdy-hey. That's me.
真希望我的朋友们能来分享,哇赛,是我耶
I'm on a yo-yo.
我有溜溜球
(胡迪牛仔秀)
Nice teeth. And yet, still a good-lookin' guy.
洁白的牙齿,帅气依然不减
(孤儿)
It's a bank! Cool.
这是存钱筒,酷毙了
What do you do? You push the hat, and out co...
这是什么?只要按一下
Out come bubbles. Clever.
就会吹泡泡,真高明
Wow. What's this thing do?
这玩意是做什么的?
I get it.
我懂了
"There's a snake in my boot."
我的靴子里有蛇
Hey, Bullseye. Go long! Go long!
红心,向前跑
A record player!
一台老唱机
I haven't seen one of these in ages.
我好久没看到这个了
OK, now. Slow.
好了,现在慢一点
That's funny, Bullseye.
好好笑哦,红心
Hop on, cowgirl! Think fast!
上来吧,女牛仔,快一点
- Not bad. - It's time for Woody's Roundup
- 不错嘛 - 胡迪牛仔秀,大家一起玩
He's the very best
他是西部
He's the rootin'-est tootin'-est cowboy...
最棒最酷最炫的警长
Look at us! We're a complete set!
你看,我们凑成一整组了
- Now it's on to the museum. - Museum?
- 现在可以去博物馆了 - 博物馆?
- What museum? - The museum.
- 什么博物馆? - 独一无二的博物馆
We're being sold to the Konishi Toy Museum in Tokyo.
我们被卖到东京的小西玩具博物馆
- That's in japan! - Japan?
- 在日本耶 - 日本?
No, no, no, no, no. I can't go to japan.
不行,我不能去日本
What do you mean?
什么意思?
I've got to get back home to my owner, Andy.
我得回去找我的主人安弟
Hey, look, look. See?
你们看
- He still has an owner. - My goodness.
- 他还有主人 - 我的老天
No. Can't go.
我…不要
I can't do storage again. I just can't!
我不要回去储藏室
- Jessie. - I won't go back in the dark!
- 翠丝 - 我不要回到黑暗中
What's the matter? What's wrong with her?
她是怎么了?
Well, we've been in storage for a long time
我们一直被关在储藏室
waiting for you.
等你来
- Why me? - The museum's
- 为什么? - 一定要有你
only interested in the collection if you're in it, Woody.
博物馆才肯收藏我们
Without you, we go back into storage.
没有你,我们就得回储藏室
- It's that simple. - It's not fair!
- 就这么简单 - 不公平
How can you do this to us?
你怎么可以这样?
Hey, look. I'm sorry, but this is all a big mistake.
对不起,这是个错误
- You see, I was in this yard sale... - Yard sale?
- 我在前院拍卖时被… - 前院拍卖?
Why were you in a yard sale if you have an owner?
如果你有主人,怎么会被拍卖?
Well, I wasn't supposed to be there. I was trying to save another toy when...
我只是去救一个朋友
Was it because you're damaged? Did this Andy break you?
是因为你坏了吗?安弟把你弄坏了吗?
Yeah, but... No, no, no, no, no! It was... It was an accident.
对,但是…不对!那只是个意外
- I mean... - Sounds like he really loves you.
- 我的意思是... - 听起来他真是爱惜你
It's not like that, OK? And I'm not going to any museum!
才不是这样,我也不想去博物馆
Well, I'm not going back into storage!
我也不想回储藏室
Al's coming!
艾而回来了
Go! Go on, jessie.
翠丝,跳进去
Jessie, look at me.
翠丝,看着我
I promise you'll come out of the box... Now go! Go!
我保证你一定出得来,快跳进去吧
It's show time!
好戏登场了
Money, baby. Money, money, money.
钱来也…钱来也…
And now, the main attraction.
现在轮到男主角登场
No! His arm! Where's his arm?
不!他的手呢?
No...No!
糟了,不!
What am I gonna do? I know. I know.
我该怎么办?我知道了
Come on! Come on! Come on! Pick up the phone!
快接…快接电话
- Hello? - It's me. It's Al.
- 喂? - 是我艾而
I got an emergency.
我有紧急状况
- I'm busy. - Yes, we're all busy.
- 我在忙 - 大家都在忙
Look. It has to be tonight.
你今晚一定要过来
All right. All right. But first thing in the morning.
好吧,明天一大早就来
It's gone! I can't believe it!
完了,天啊,我不敢相信
- My arm is completely gone! - All right. Come here. Let me see that.
- 我的手断了 - 过来让我瞧瞧
It's just a popped seam, easily repaired.
只是线断了,很容易补的
- You should consider yourself lucky. - Lucky?
- 算你走运 - 走运?
Are you shrink-wrapped? I am missing my arm!
你是老糊涂吗?我的手断了耶
Big deal.
那又怎样?
(嗨,大家好)
Let him go. I'm sure his precious Andy
让他走吧,他的主人这么好
is dying to play with a one-armed cowboy doll.
一定很想跟一个,独臂牛仔玩的
Why, jessie, you know he wouldn't last an hour on the streets in his condition.
翠丝,你知道他这种情况,在外头撑不了一小时
It's a dangerous world out there for a toy.
外面的世界对玩具而言,太危险了
All right. Nobody look till I get my cork back in.
在我赛好之前别偷看
Good work, men. Two blocks down and only 19 more to go.
干得好,走了两条街,剩下十九条街
- What? - Nineteen?
- 什么? - 十九条街?
Are we gonna do this all night? My parts are killing me.
还要多久啊?我快累毙了
Come on, fellas.
别这样
Did Woody give up when Sid had me strapped to a rocket?
我被小薛抓走胡迪有放弃吗?没有
And did he give up when you threw him out of the back of that moving van?
没错,你把他踢下卡车,他有放弃吗?
- You had to bring that up. - No, he didn't!
- 你非得提这档事吗? - 他没有放弃
We have a friend in need, and we will not rest until he's safe in Andy's room!
有一个朋友需要我们,我们一定要把他安全救回家
Now let's move out!
继续前进
And that concludes our broadcast day.
今天的节目全部播放完毕
Bullseye. Bullseye, go, go, go, go.
红心,走开
Come on. You don't wanna help me. I'm the bad guy.
别帮我的忙,我是坏人,记得吗?
You're gonna go back in storage because of me, remember? Just go.
我会害你们被收起来,快走开
Bullseye... All right. All right.
好啦,好啦
But you have got to keep quiet. Come on.
但是你不能出声,来吧
Over here. Attaboy.
过来,好马儿
OK, Bullseye. Upsy-daisy.
好了,把我抬起来
Bullseye. Cut it out.
红心,别乱来
Stop it. Stop it, Bullseye. Stop it. Stop it.
别这样,红心
Stop it.
别闹了
Woody's Roundup Come on it's time to play
胡迪牛仔秀,大家一起玩
No, Officer! I swear. What?
警察先生,我发誓我没有…
Get in there. There you go. Cheap case.
进去吧,好了,烂盒子
Where is the remote? Where is the remote?
电视遥控器呢?遥控器呢?
Why don't I put it in the same place every... Here it is.
我每次都乱放…在这儿
What is your problem?
你太卑鄙了
Look, I'm sorry I can't help you guys out.
很抱歉我帮不了你
Really, I am. But you didn't have to go and pull a stunt like that.
不过你也不必耍这一招
What? You think I did that?
你说是我干的
Right. The TV just happened to turn on,
是啊,难道电视会自动打开
and the remote magically ended up in front of you!
遥控器会自己,飞到你面前吗?
- You calling me a liar? - Well, if the boot fits...
- 你是说我是骗子吗? - 你是不打自招
Say that again.
再说一次
If the boot fits.
你是不打自招
OK, cowboy.
好吧,牛仔
How do you like that? Take it back! Take it back!
尝到苦头了吧,把话收回去,收回去
Don't think just 'cause you're a girl, I'm gonna take it easy on you.
别以为你是女孩子,我就会饶过你
Jessie, Woody, you stop this at once.
翠丝、胡迪,马上住手
(拿丁字鎚的玩偶他还会说话哟)
(胡迪牛仔秀系列玩具)
I don't know how that television turned on,
我不知道电视怎么会打开
but fighting about it isn't helping anything.
不过打架没有用
- If I had both my arms... - The fact is, you don't, Woody,
- 要是我的双手健全… - 你没有双手
so I suggest you just wait until morning.
所以你最好等到早上
- The cleaner will come, fix. Your arm... - And then I'm outta here!
- 工匠会来修补你 - 然后我就走人
Oh, no, no. Bullseye, don't take it that way.
红心,你不要这样
- It's just that Andy... - Andy, Andy, Andy.
- 只是安弟… - 安弟…安弟…
That's all he ever talks about.
他只关心安弟
Hey, Buzz, can we slow down?
巴斯,慢一点好吗?
May I remind you that some of us are carrying over six. Dollars in change?
我要提醒你,我可是身怀巨款耶
Losing health units. Must rest.
能量减低,必须休息
- Is everyone present and accounted for? - Not quite everyone.
- 大家都到齐了吗? - 还没有
- Who's behind? - Mine.
- 谁落后了? - 我的屁股
Hey, guys. Why do the toys cross the road?
大伙儿,玩具为什么要过马路?
- Not now, Hamm. - I love riddles. Why?
- 火腿,别闹了 - 我最爱猜迷,为什么?
To get to the chicken on the other side!
为了到对面的公鸡城
(艾而玩具城)
The chicken!
是那只公鸡
- Oh, well. We tried. - We'll have to cross.
- 我们已经尽了力 - 我们一定要过马路
What the...
什么?
You're not turning me into a mashed potato.
我可不想变成洋芋泥
I may not be a smart dog, but I know what roadkill is.
我虽然不聪明,但是我知道马路如虎口
There must be a safe way.
一定有安全的办法
OK. Here's our chance. Ready. Set. Go.
机会来了,预备,走吧
Drop!
停!
Go!
走
Drop! I said "drop"!
停!我说停!
Go!
走
Drop.
停
Go.
走
That went well.
挺顺利的嘛
Good job, troops. We're that much closer to Woody.
大伙儿,干得好,就快找到胡迪了
Thank goodness you're here.
谢天谢地,你终于来了
Is the specimen ready for cleaning?
这里有玩具要修理吗?
So how long is this gonna take?
你要花多久时间?
You can't rush art.
这是艺术,急不得
(艾而玩具城)
(休息中)
Oh, no. It's closed.
糟糕,休息了
We're not preschool toys, Slinky. We can read.
我又不是学龄前玩具,我识字
Hey, joe, you're late.
你迟到了
We've got a ton of toys to unload.
快工作吧
All right. All right. I'm comin'. I'm comin'.
好啦,我来了啦
All right. Let's go.
好了,走吧
But the sign says it's closed.
可是上面写“休息了”耶
No, no, no, no. All together. Now!
等等,一起来,跳!
(击败札克天王必胜秘笈)
(想击败札克天王?)
Whoa, Nelly! How are we going to find Woody in this place?
我的妈,地方这么大怎么找呀?
Look for Al. We find Al, we find Woody. Now move out!
只要找到艾而,就能找到胡迪,出发
- Woody? - Woody.
- 胡迪? - 胡迪
(安弟)
There you go.
好了
He's for display only.
他是展示品
You handle him too much, he's not gonna last.
一直玩的话就会坏掉
It's amazing. You're a genius. He's just like new.
不可思议,你是个天才,他就像全新的
(全新)
(太空骑警巴斯光年)
Wow.
哇赛
(全新配备)
I could use one of those.
这玩意我倒是用得上
(太空骑警巴斯光年)
You know, they make it so you can't defeat Zurg unless you buy this book.
一定要卖这本书,才能打败札克
It's extortion. That's what it is.
这简直是敲诈嘛
Hey, I always thought the golden sector was the only...
我以为黄金宝杖是用来…
I thought we could search in style.
这样找起来比较拉风
Nice going there, Hamm. So how about letting a toy with fingers drive?
干得好,火腿,你没有手指,我来开车
Am I really that fat?
我真的有这么胖吗?
- What are you doing? - You're in direct violation
- 你在干嘛? - 你直接违反了...
of Code 6404.5,
你违反了6404.5条规
stating all space rangers are to be in hyper-sleep
太空战警一定要留在睡眠舱
until awakened by authorized personnel.
等待上级的指令
Oh, no.
不是吧
You're breakin' ranks, ranger.
你这是脱队行动
Buzz Lightyear to Star Command.
巴斯光年呼叫星际总部
- I've got an AWOL space ranger. - Tell me I wasn't this deluded.
- 这儿有一名逃兵 - 我以前没这么神经吧?
No back talk! I have a laser, and I will use it.
不准顶嘴,我有雷射光,别逼我使用它
You mean the laser that's a light bulb?
什么雷射,它只是灯泡
Has your mind been melded? You could've killed me, space ranger.
你是脑袋有问题吗?你差点把我害死
Or should I say "traitor"?
你这个星际叛徒
- I don't have time for this. - Halt!
- 我没时间跟你穷蘑菇 - 停下
I order you to halt!
我命令你站住
Listen to me. Listen. Wait.
听我说,听好
- We've been down this aisle already. - We've never been down this aisle.
- 这条通道走过了 - 才没有
- It's pink. - Face it. We're lost.
- 这排是粉红色的 - 我们迷路了
Back it up. Back it up.
退后,退后
What a great party!
好棒的派对
How low can you go? How low can you go?
你能弯多低?你能弯多低?
Ex. Cuse me, ladies.
美女们
Does anyone know where we might find the Al of Al's Toy Barn?
你们知道艾而在哪儿吗?
I can help.
我来帮忙
I'm Tour Guide Barbie.
我是导游芭比
Please keep your hands, arms and accessories inside the car,
请别把头手和配件伸出车外
and no flash photography.
请别用闪光灯
- Thank you. - I'm a married spud. I'm a married spud.
- 谢谢 - 我是有妇之夫…
Then make room for the single fellas.
那就把机会让给单身汉
To our right is the Hot Wheels aisle. Developed in 1967,
右手边是模型汽车系列,1967年系列有16辆车
the original series had 16 cars, including the Corvette.
包括雪佛兰跑车
I beg your pardon, ma'am, but where's Al's office?
对不起,小姐,请问,艾而的办公室在哪儿?
Please hold all questions until the end of the tour. Thank you.
请在导览之后再发问,感谢您
It says how you defeat Zurg! Look!
上面教你怎么打败札克天王
- Excuse me, sir. - Get this outta here, "geek-osaur."
- 打扰一下,先生 - 抱抱龙,快拿开
- Look out! - Stop, stop, stop!
- 小心! - 停车!停车!
Turn into the spin, Barbie!
方向盘打直
My source of power!
我的必胜秘笈
No! Come back! Hey!
回来!
Wait up! Hey! Come on! Slow down!
等等我,慢一点
Dinosaur overboard! Slow down!
恐龙在后面,慢一点
Remain seated, please.
请留在座位上
[西班牙语]
Listen to me. Listen to me. You're not really a space ranger.
听我说,你不是太空战警
You're a toy. We're all toys. Do you hear me?
你是个玩具,我们都是玩具
Well, that should hold you till the court martial.
你等着受军法审判吧
Let me go! You don't realize what you're doing!
放开我,你搞不懂状况
And this is the Buzz Lightyear aisle.
这里是巴斯光年区
In 1995, shortsighted retailers did not order enough dolls to meet demand.
1995那年,巴斯光年玩偶供不应求
- Hey, Buzz! - Halt! Who goes there?
- 巴斯 - 停车,你们是谁?
Quit clownin' around and get in the car!
别闹了,上车吧
Buzz, Buzz, I know how to defeat Zurg!
巴斯 我知道该怎么击败札克
- You do? - Come on. I'll tell you on the way.
- 真的吗? - 上车后我再告诉你
No, no, guys! You've got the wrong Buzz! You've got the wrong Buzz!
大伙儿,他不是真的巴斯,你们认错人了
Say, where'd you get the cool belt, Buzz?
这么酷的皮带哪来的?
Well, slotted pig, they're standard issue.
猪扑满,这是标准配备
(西部服饰  牛仔头巾)
(和胡迪一起学弹吉他)
It's like printing my own money.
我就像在印钞票一样
Yeah? What?
喂,干嘛?
Mr. Konishi. Yes, I have the pictures right here.
小西先生,是的,照片都在这儿
In fact, I'm in the car right now on my way to the office to fax. Them to you.
我正开车赶去办公室,准备传真给你
I'm going through a tunnel! I'm breakin' up!
我在过隧道,讯号不清楚
Wow! Will you look at me? It's like I'm fresh out of the box!
你们看,我真是焕然一新
Look at this stitching! Andy's gonna have a hard time rippin' this! Hello!
他缝得好牢,这下安弟一定扯不坏
Hi! Hello!
嗨,你好
Great. Now you can go.
太好了,你可以走了
Well, what a good idea.
真是个好主意
Woody, don't be mad at jessie.
胡迪,别生翠丝的气
She's been through more than you know.
她受的苦也夠多了
Why not make amends before you leave, huh?
你在走之前跟她和好吧
It's the least you can do.
这是你应该做的
All right. But I don't know what good it'll do.
好吧,不过没什么用
Hey. Whatcha doin' way up here?
你在上面干嘛?
Thought I'd get one last look at the sun before I get packed away again.
我想再看太阳一眼,然后就会永远被关起来
Look, jessie. I know you hate me for leaving,
我知道你很恨我
but I have to go back.
但是我一定要回家
I'm still Andy's toy.
我还是安弟的玩具
Well, if you knew him, you'd understand. Andy's a real...
要是你认识安弟,一定会了解…
Let me guess. Andy's a real special kid.
让我猜,他是个特别的小孩
And to him, you're his buddy, his best friend.
你是他最好的朋友
And when Andy plays with you, it's like even though you're not moving,
只要安弟跟你一起玩,虽然你不会动
you feel like you're alive, because that's how he sees you.
你却觉得自己是活的,因为他也认为你是真的
How did you know that?
你怎么知道?
Because Emily was just the same.
因为爱咪莉也一样
She was my whole world.
她是我的一切
When somebody loved me
当我有人爱
Everything was beautiful
一切都美好
Every hour we spent together
每一分每一秒
Lives within my heart
都活在我心中
And when she was sad
每当她流泪
I was there to dry her tears
我为她擦干
And when she was happy so was I
每当她开心,我也很快乐
When she loved me
当她还爱我
Through the summer and the fall
不管寒冬或酷暑
We had each other That was all
只要有彼此,我们不寂莫
Just she and I together
我跟她一起
Like it was meant to be
永远相偎依
And when she was lonely
每当她孤单
I was there to comfort her
我就陪着她
And I knew that
我也知道
She loved me
她爱我
So the years went by
一年一年过去
I stayed the same
我还是一样
But she began to drift away
她却越走越远
I was left alone
丢下我一个
Still I waited for the day
但我仍然期待她
When she'd say
说一声
I will always
我永远…
Love you
…都爱你
Lonely and forgotten
于是我痴痴的等
I never thought she'd look my way
希望她再看一眼
She smiled at me and held me
终于她笑着抱着我
Just like she used to do
就像美好的从前
Like she loved me
她是那么地爱我
When she loved me
疼我
When somebody loved me
当我有人爱
Everything was beautiful
一切都美好
Every hour we spent together
每一分每一秒
Lives within my heart
都活在我心中
When she loved me
当她还爱我
You never forget kids like Emily or Andy.
我们忘不了爱咪莉或安弟
But they forget you.
但是他们会忘了我们
- Jessie, I... I didn't know. - Just go.
- 翠丝,我不知道 - 你走吧
How long will it last, Woody?
友情能维持多久?
Do you really think Andy is gonna take you to college
你真的以为安弟,会带你一起上大学
or on his honeymoon?
或是度蜜月吗?
Andy's growing up,
安弟会长大
and there's nothing you can do about it.
你无法阻止他
It's your choice, Woody.
你有两个选择
You can go back, or you can stay with us and last forever.
你可以回去,或是跟我们一起永远保存
You'll be adored by children for generations.
受到世世代代小孩的喜爱
Who am I to break up the Roundup gang?
我算哪根葱,怎么能拆散“胡迪牛仔秀”?
- Hey, Woody, are you in here? - Nah. This one's empty too.
- 胡迪,你在吗? - 这也是空盒子
- Woody! Woody! - Woody!
- 胡迪 胡迪 - 胡迪
Pardon me, gentlemen, but have either of you seen a cowboy doll with a bad arm?
打扰了,请问两位,有没有看到断手的牛仔?
- Why, no, I haven't. - Hey! He was talkin' to me!
- 没有耶 - 嘿,他在跟我讲话
- No! He was talkin' to me! - Why, you...
- 他是在跟我讲话 - 可恶
You see, all along,
我们一直以为
we thought the way into Zurg's fortress was through the main gate,
入口是札克城堡的大门
but in fact, the secret entrance is to the left, hidden in the shadows.
其实秘密入口在左边,藏在阴影底下
To the left in the shadows. Got it.
左边的阴影下,知道了
- Someone's coming. - Everyone, take cover.
- 有人来了 - 大家快找掩护
It was a big pile-up, but I don't want to bore you with the details.
路上大赛车,就甭提了
Yes. Now, let me confirm your fax. Number.
请问你的传真几号?
Wait.
等等
That's a lot of numbers. No. I got it.
好多号码哦,知道了
- It's him. - The chicken man.
- 是他 - 公鸡人
Funny, he doesn't look like poultry.
奇怪,他一点都不像家禽
That's the kidnapper, all right.
他就是绑匪没错
A kidnapper! An agent of Zurg if I ever saw one.
他才不是绑匪,他是札克的爪牙
And the piece de resistance!
这就是我的无价之宝
I promise the collection will be the crown jewel of your museum.
我保证这会是,你最耀眼的收藏品
- It's Woody! - Now that I have your attention,
- 那是胡迪 - 这些货你都看了
imagine we added another zero to the price, huh?
我要在价钱后面加一个零吗?
- I'll pay anything you want. - Yes! Yes!
- 你要多少钱都行 - 棒呆了
You got a deal! I'll be on the next flight to japan!
咱们一言为定,我搭下一班机到日本
Quick. Into the poultry man's cargo unit.
快跳进家禽人的货舱
He'll lead us to Zurg. Move, move, move!
他会带我们找到札克,快…快…
Don't touch my moustache!
莎哟娜啦,再见啰
Rich, rich, rich, rich!
发了!发了!
(巴斯光年死敌  札克天王)
(看这里)
(札克天王远视镜)
Destroy Buzz Lightyear.
消灭巴斯光年
Destroy Buzz Lightyear. Destroy Buzz Lightyear.
消灭巴斯光年…
- He didn't take the bag! - No time to lose!
- 他没拿走袋子 - 不能浪费时间
He's ascending in the vertical transporter.
他搭乘垂直输送机
All right, everyone. Hang on. We're gonna blast through the roof.
抓紧了,我们要冲到屋顶
- Buzz? - To infinity and beyond!
- 巴斯 - 飞向宇宙…浩瀚无垠
What are you? Insane? We're wasting time. Stand still, Godzilla.
你秀逗啦?别浪费时间,站好了,抱抱龙
I don't understand.
我搞不懂
Somehow my fuel cells have gone dry.
我的电瓶怎么会没有电
Blast. He's on level 23.
糟了,他到了23楼
How are we gonna get up there?
我们该怎么上去?
Maybe if we find some balloons, we could float to the top.
我们可以找几个气球漂上去
Are you kidding? I say we stack ourselves up,
别开玩笑了,我们叠罗汉
push the intercom and pretend we're delivering a pizza.
再按对讲机,假扮我们在送比萨
How about a ham sandwich... with fries and a hot dog?
火腿三明治薯条加热狗,怎么样?
What about me?
那我呢?
You can be the toy that comes with the meal.
你是随餐附赠玩具
Troops! Over here.
弟兄们,这儿
Just like you said, lizard man. "In the shadows to the left."
大蜥蜴,跟你说的一样,入口在左边的阴影下
OK. Let's move!
出动
Mission log. Have infiltrated enemy territory without detection
任务日志,我们潜入敌区
and are making our way through the bowels of Zurg's fortress.
进入札克天王的城堡
You know, I think that Buzz aisle went to his head.
我看他是被冲昏了头
Oh, no. Which way do we go?
糟糕,往哪个方向?
- This way! - What makes you so sure?
- 这边 - 你怎么这么有把握?
I'm Buzz Lightyear. I'm always sure.
巴斯光年从不做没把握的事
We've been detected. The walls! They're closing in! Quick!
我们被发现了,墙壁会把我们夹死
Help me prop up vegetable man, or we're done for.
马铃薯快帮我挡一下
Hey! Put me down, you moron!
笨蛋,快放我下来
Guys, look! It's not the walls! It's the elevator!
不是墙啦,是电梯
Come on. We've got no time to lose. Everyone, grab hold!
我们来不及了,大伙儿,抓住我
What?
什么?
Buzz, why not just take the elevator?
巴斯,为什么不直接坐电梯?
They'll be ex. Pecting that.
这招会被他们料到
(残障停车位)
Hey, Buzz! Stop!
巴斯,等等
Slow down!
慢一点
To overnight six. Packages to japan is how much?
六件隔天要送到日本的,快捷包裹要多少钱?
- What? That's in yen, right? - No dollars sir.
- 什么? - 是日园吧?
- Dollars? - Yes.
- 美元? - 是的
You are deliberately taking advantage of people in a hurry, you know that?
我在赶时间,你们是故意抢钱耶
All right. I'll do it! All right. Fine.
好啦…好吧
I'll have the stuff in the lobby, and you'd better be here in 15 minutes,
我会在大厅等,你们最好十五分钟后到
because I have a plane to catch, do you hear me?
我要赶飞机,听到吗?
We're finally going. Can you believe it?
我们终于要走了,你相信吗?
That's custom-fitted foam insulation you'll be riding in, Bullseye.
那是特别订做的箱子
First class all the way!
这一趟要坐头等舱
You know what? I'm actually ex. Cited about this.
老实说,我觉得很兴奋
I mean it. I really am!
我是说真的
And why shouldn't you be?
那是当然了
Swing your partner do-si-do
跟着舞伴左摇右晃
- Look at you, dancing cowboy! - Look! I'm doin' the box. Step!
- 你是个跳舞的牛仔 - 瞧,我在跳方块舞耶
Hey, heads up down there!
下面小心点
- Pork bellies are fallin'. - Hey, how much farther, Buzz?
- 猪肚掉下来了 - 还有多远呀?
Halfway there.
就快到了
My arms can't hold on much longer!
我的手撑不下去了
Too... heavy.
太重了
What was I thinking?
我真傻
My antigravity servos!
我有反重力功能
Hang tight, everyone. I'm going to let go of the wall.
抓紧了,我要放手了
- What? - He wouldn't.
- 什么? - 他不会吧
- One... - He would.
- 一 - 他会
Two...
二,别放手…
Three!
三!
To infinity and beyond!
飞向宇宙…浩瀚无垠
Approaching destination. Reengaging gravity.
接近目标,恢复重力
Area secure.
安全
It's OK, troops.
没事了
The antigravity sickness will wear off momentarily. Now let's move!
反重力引起的晕眩,马上就会消失,前进吧
Remind me to glue his helmet shut when we get back.
记得提醒我回去以后,要好好教训他一顿
How 'bout givin' me a little intro there, jessie?
翠丝,介绍我出场吧
Introducing the high-ridin'-est cowboy around...
我要介绍,西部最棒最酷的牛仔
You forgot "rootin'-tootin'-est"!
你忘了说最炫
The high-ridin'-est, rootin'-tootin'-est cowboy hero of all time,
西部最棒最酷,最炫的牛仔英雄
Sheriff Woody!
胡迪警长
Say, little missy, you notice any trouble around these parts?
嘿,小妞,这儿有麻烦吗?
Nary a bit, not with Sheriff Woody around.
没有,胡迪警长会搞定一切
Wait-wait-wait! I got it! This is great! OK!
等等,我有了
The bandits got the critters tied up in the burning barn. Now the best part!
强盗把小动物,关在着火的壳仓
Help us! The barn's on fire!
救命呀,壳仓着火了
I've got ya, critters. No need to worry.
我来了,别害怕
Woody saves the day again!
胡迪又解除了危机
Now, where's my trusty steed Bullseye?
我的爱马红心呢?
I have to ride off into the sunset...
我得潇洒的骑向落日
Ride like the wind, Bullseye!
快马加鞭吧,红心
Watch it. Wait. I'm ticklish, OK?
别这样,我怕痒
Oh, you are?
是吗?
No, no, no. Cut it out. Stop it. Stop it.
住手,别这样
No, please. No, no. Stop! Stop!
快住手,住手
Mission log. Have reached Zurg's command deck,
任务日志,这是札克的指挥舱
but no sign of him or his wooden captive.
没有他和木头俘虏的踪影
- Please, no! - That's Woody!
- 不要! - 那是胡迪
This way!
这里
Please, please, no!
拜托,住手
Buzz, can you see? What's going on?
你看得到吗?怎么回事?
- Take that! - To the left.
- 拿着 - 左边
No, your left.
你的左边啦
- Take it up higher. - What's happening?
- 高一点 - 怎么回事?
It's horrible. They're torturing him.
太可怕了,他们在拷问他
- What are we gonna do, Buzz? - Use your head!
- 我们该怎么办? - 用用你的脑袋
But I don't wanna use my head!
但是我不想要用我的脑袋
What's going on here?
这是怎么回事?
Buzz, guys! Hey, how did you find me?
巴斯,大伙儿,你们怎么找得到我?
Watch yourself!
小心点
We're here to spring ya, Woody!
我们来救你了
You heard of kung fu?
听过无影腿吗?
Well, get ready for pork chop.
尝尝我的火腿
Prepare to meet Mr. Angry Eyes!
见识我愤怒双眼的威力
Hold it, now! Hey, you don't understand! These are my friends!
等等,你们搞错了,他们是我的朋友
- Yeah, we're his friends! - No, Rex, I mean they're my friends!
- 没错,我们是他的朋友 - 不是啦,我是说他们
Hey, stop it! You leave him alone, springy dog!
站住,笨狗,给我放开他
- Grab Woody, and let's go! - Fellas, hold it!
- 快去救胡迪 - 伙计们,等等
- Buzz, put me down! - Quick! To the vent!
- 巴斯,放我下来 - 撤退,冲到通风孔
- They're stealing him! - No!
- 他被抢走了 - 不
Hold it right there!
大伙儿别动
- Buzz? - You again?
- 巴斯 - 又是你
Woody! Thank goodness you're all right.
胡迪,幸好你没事
Buzz, what is going on?
这是怎么回事?
Hold on. I am Buzz Lightyear, and I'm in charge of this detachment.
慢着,我是巴斯光年,这里由我指挥
No, I'm Buzz Lightyear.
我才是巴斯光年
- I'm Buzz Lightyear! - I'm Buzz Lightyear!
- 我是巴斯光年 - 我才是
So, who's the real Buzz?
谁是真的巴斯?
- I am! - I am!
- 我是! - 我是!
Don't let this impostor fool you!
别上这个冒牌货的当
He's been trained by Zurg himself to mimic my every move.
札克训练他模仿,我的一举一动
(安弟)
Buzz!
巴斯
I had a feelin' it was you.
我就知道是你
My front end just had to catch up with my back end.
只是我有时候头尾不分
Will somebody please ex. Plain what's going on?
请你们解释好吗?
It's all right, space ranger. It's a code 546.
没事了,太空战警,这是546密令
- You mean it's a... - Yes.
- 你是说… - 没错
- And he's a... - Oh, yeah.
- 他就是… - 是的
Your Majesty.
陛下
Woody, you're in danger here. We need to leave now.
胡迪,你有危险,快走吧
Al's selling you to a museum in japan!
艾而要把你卖到,日本的博物馆
I know. It's OK, Buzz. I actually wanna go.
我知道,没关系,其实我也想去
- What? - Are you crazy?
- 什么? - 你疯啦?
Look, the thing is, I'm a rare Sheriff Woody doll,
我是稀有的胡迪警长玩偶
and these guys are my Roundup gang.
他们是我的牛仔秀伙伴
- What are you talking about? - Woody's Roundup!
- 你在说什么呀? - 胡迪牛仔秀
It's this great old TV show, and I was the star. See? Now look.
我是一个电视节目的明星
Look! Look at me! See? That's me!
你看,你们看,那是我耶
- This is weirdin' me out. - Buzz, it was a national phenomenon.
- 我受不了了 - 我曾经轰动一时
There was all this merchandise that got packed up. You should have seen it.
我还有一大堆周边商品,你们应该瞧瞧
There was a record player and a yo-yo. Buzz, I was a yo-yo!
唱机、溜溜球,我曾经是溜溜球耶
- "Was"? - Stop this nonsense and let's go.
- 曾经? - 别说傻话了,咱们走吧
Buzz.
巴斯
I can't go. I can't abandon these guys.
我不能丢下这些朋友
They need me to get into this museum.
他们需要我才能进博物馆
Without me, they'll go back into storage. Maybe forever!
否则他们就得回去储藏室,永远被关起来
Woody, you're not a collector's item. You're a child's plaything.
你不是收藏品,你是给小孩玩的
You are a toy!
你是个玩具
For how much longer? One more rip, and Andy's done with me.
我还能撑多久?我再被扯破安弟就会抛弃我
And what do I do then, Buzz? Huh? You tell me.
到时候我该怎么办?你倒是说啊
Somewhere in that pad of stuffing is a toy who taught me
我记得你曾经告诉我
that life's only worth living if you're bein' loved by a kid.
当有小孩爱你时生命才有价值
And I traveled all this way to rescue that toy
我大老远跑来救你
because I believed him.
因为我相信你的话
Well, you wasted your time.
你白跑一趟了
- Let's go, everyone. - What about Woody?
- 走吧,大伙儿 - 胡迪呢?
He's not coming with us.
他不跟来了
But... But Andy's coming home tonight.
今晚安弟要回家耶
Then we'd better make sure we're there waiting for him.
那我们最好赶回去等他
I don't have a choice, Buzz. This is my only chance.
我别无选择,这是我唯一的机会
To do what, Woody? Watch kids from behind glass and never be loved again?
什么机会?永远隔着玻璃,看着小孩玩吗?
Some life.
真可悲
- Is everybody OK? - Sheriff Woody!
- 大家都没事吧? - 胡迪警长
- I knew you'd make it! - Now remember deputies
- 你救了我们 - 记住了,小朋友
the real treasures are your friends and family.
家人和朋友才是你们的一切
Before I go kids I want to share somethin' special with you
我在走之前,想要跟你们...
- for the times I'm not around. - Good going, Woody!
- 分享这首歌 - 太好了
I thought they'd never leave.
终于摆脱他们了
You've got a friend in me
我是你好朋友
- Woody? - You've got troubles
- 胡迪 - 如果你有麻烦
Well I've got 'em too
我会来帮忙
There isn't anything I wouldn't do for you
我愿为你赴汤蹈火
We stick together and see it through
只要团结就能解决
'Cause you've got a friend in me
因为我是你好朋友
Some other folks might be a little bit smarter than I am
也许别人比我聪明一点
Bigger and stronger too
也比我高大比我强
Maybe
也许吧
But none of them will ever love you
但是从来没有人
The way I do
像我这么爱你
It's me and you boy
我们是好朋友
And as the years go by
一年一年过去
Our friendship will never die
我们的友谊更加坚固
- What am I doing? - You're gonna see it's our destiny
- 我这是在干嘛? - 你会发现这是我们的命...
- Buzz! Wait! Wait! - Woody, where are you going?
- 巴斯,等等我 - 你要去哪里?
You're right, Prospector. I can't stop Andy from growing up.
你说得对,安弟一定会长大
But I wouldn't miss it for the world.
但是我不想错过每一刻
- No! - Buzz!
- 不! - 巴斯
- Yes? - Yes?
- 干嘛? - 干嘛?
I'm coming with you!
我要跟你们走
Wait... wait... wait. I'll be back in just a second.
等一下,我马上回来
Way to go, cowboy!
干得好,牛仔
- Hey, you guys... Come with me. - What?
- 大伙儿,跟我一起来吧 - 什么?
Andy will play with all of us. I know it!
安弟会跟我们一起玩
Woody, I... I... I don't know. I...
胡迪,我不晓得耶
Wouldn't you give anything just to have one more day with Emily?
难道你不想再陪伴爱咪莉吗?
Come on, jessie. This is what it's all about: To make a child happy.
翠丝,最重要的是,让一个小孩快乐
And you know it. Bullseye, are you with me?
你心里很明白,红心,你来不来?
OK, good boy.
好马儿
Prospector, how 'bout you?
老矿工,你说呢?
- Prospector? - You're outta your box!
- 老矿工? - 你离开盒子了
I tried reasoning with you, Woody,
我试着跟你讲道理
but you keep forcing me to take extreme measures.
但是你逼得我不择手段
Wait a minute. You turned on the TV last night, not jessie.
昨晚是你打开电视,不是翠丝
Look, we have an eternity to spend together in the museum.
我们要永远一起留在博物馆
Let's not start off by pointing fingers, shall we?
你不要破坏咱们之间的感情
You really are Stinky Pete, aren't you?
你真的很可恶耶
Prospector, this isn't fair.
老矿工,这样很不公平
"Fair"? I'll tell you what's not fair.
不公平?什么叫不公平?
Spending a lifetime on a dime-store shelf watching every other toy be sold.
我一辈子都坐在架子上,看着别的玩具被卖走
Well, finally my waiting has paid off,
现在我终于熬出头
and no hand-me-down cowboy doll is gonna mess it up for me now!
一个臭牛仔,休想坏了我的好事
Buzz. Help, Buzz! Guys!
巴斯,救命呀,巴斯
It's too late, Woody. That silly Buzz Lightweight can't help you.
太迟了,那个撒隆巴斯帮不了你
His name is Buzz Lightyear.
他的名字是巴斯光年
Whatever. I've always hated those upstart space toys.
随便啦,我最讨厌太空玩具了
It's stuck! What do we do?
卡住了,怎么办?
Should I use my head?
要用我脑袋吗?
It's Al!
是艾而
Look at the time. I'm gonna be late!
我快赶不及了
Figures. I can't miss this flight! I've gotta pack.
我不能错过班机,我得打包
All right. Let's see. Wallet, keys, tickets,
钱包、钥匙、机票
passport, beef jerky, very ex. Pensive over there.
护照、牛肉干…在日本很贵
Shower! I can skip the shower.
洗澡,来不及洗了
I just gotta get outta here now!
我得走了
Quick! To the elevator!
快去坐电梯
Hurry. I can hear it coming.
快点,电梯来了
So, we meet again, Buzz Lightyear,
巴斯光年,我们又见面了
for the last time.
这次你死定了
It's Zurg! Watch out! He's got an ion blaster!
是札克天王,小心,他有离子炮
Quick! Get on!
快上电梯
The emergency hatch! Come on!
紧急逃生口,快点
- Come on! Hurry! - But Buzz is in peril!
- 来吧,快点 - 巴斯有危险耶
Buzz... Buzz... Buzz... Lightyear to the rescue!
巴斯光年…拯救世界
Surrender, Buzz Lightyear. I have won.
投降吧,巴斯光年,我赢了
I'll never give in. You killed my father!
我不会投降,你杀了我父亲
No, Buzz. I am your father.
不,巴斯,我就是你父亲
No!
不!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
快点…快点…
Buzz, you could have defeated Zurg all along!
巴斯,你可以打败札克
You just need to believe in yourself!
你只要相信自己
- Prepare to die! - I can't look!
- 领死吧 - 我不敢看
I did it. I finally defeated Zurg!
我成功了,我终于打败札克了
Father.
爸爸
Finally!
终于到了
How are we gonna get him now?
我们该怎么救他?
Pizza, anyone?
谁要吃比萨?
(比萨星球)
- Go, go, go! - I got it!
- 快走,快走 - 我接到了
Buzz, are you coming?
巴斯,你来不来?
No, I have a lot of catching up to do with my dad.
不了,我要多陪陪我爸爸
Good throw, son. That's my boy. Go long, Buzzy!
丢得好,乖儿子,跑远一点,小巴斯
- You're a great dad. - Farewell.
- 你是个好爸爸,万岁 - 再见了
Does anyone know how to drive?
有人会开车吗?
Slink, take the pedals. Rex, you navigate.
弹簧狗,踩油门,抱抱龙,看方向
Hamm and Potato, operate the levers and knobs.
火腿和蛋头,控制按键
- Strangers. - From the outside.
- 陌生人 - 外面来的
- Oh, no. - He's at a red light! We can catch him!
- 惨了 - 是红灯,快追上去
Max. Imum power, Slink!
弹簧狗,全速前进
It turned green! Hurry!
绿灯了,快点
- Why won't it go? - Use the Wand of Power.
- 为什么不动? - 你们要用动力棍
- Rex, which way? - Left! No, no! I mean right!
- 抱抱龙,往哪儿? - 左,我是说右
That's right! No, I mean left! Left is right!
对了,左边才对
Buzz, he's turning left! He's turning left!
巴斯,他左转了
Oh, boy!
天啊
I seriously doubt he's gettin' this kind of mileage.
这辆车吃油吃得很凶
Go right! To the right! Right-right-right-right!
右转!右转!
You have saved our lives. We are eternally grateful.
你救了我们,我们永远感谢你
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Whatever.
好啦,随便啦
(国际机场)
The white zone is for immediate loading and unloading...
白线只准卸货或上下乘客
No parking.
不准停车
(远东航空)
Guys, we can't park here! It's a white zone!
不能停这儿,这是白线
You have saved our lives. We are eternally grateful.
你救了我们,我们永远感谢你
- Final boarding call... - There he is!
- 最后登机电话... - 他在那儿
... for Far East Airlines flight 451 to Tokyo.
前往东京的班机马上起飞
All confirmed passengers must board at this time.
已登记的旅客请马上登机
Passenger Twitch passenger Leon Twitch please pick up...
旅客托维奇,请和地勤人员联络…
You have saved our lives. We are eternally grateful.
你救了我们,我们永远感谢你
- Will you leave me alone? - Someone's coming!
- 别缠着我,好吗? - 有人来了
- A puppy! - Bark-bark-bark-bark.
- 小狗狗 - 汪汪汪...
Bark-bark-bark-bark-bark.
汪汪汪…
Listen, flyboy.
给我听好,小飞仔
The contents of that case are worth more than you make in a year!
箱子里的东西你赔不起
- You got that? You be careful! - I understand, sir.
- 瞭不瞭? 小心点 - 我明白
Do you have a "fragile" sticker or something?
给我小心点,没有“易碎”的标签吗?
I had a box. Of cookies once that came back as crumbs!
我带过一盒饼干,结果变成饼干屑
The Mystic Portal!
神奇的入口
Once we go through, we just need to find that case.
我们进去后,只要找到箱子就行了
- There's the case! - No, there's the case!
- 箱子在那儿 - 是那个箱子
You take that one! We'll take this one!
你去追那个,我们追这个
(屁屁)
Buzz, my back end's goin' to Baton Rouge!
巴斯,我的尾巴要往德州去了
Slinky!
弹簧狗
Here we come, Woody! Woody, here we come! Woody!
胡迪,我们来了,胡迪
Nice flash though.
好炫的闪光灯
OK, Woody, let's go!
胡迪,走吧
Take that, space toy.
吃我一拳,太空玩具
Hey! No one does that to my friend!
你不能打我的朋友
Your choice, Woody.
我警告你
You can go to japan together or in pieces.
你再不乖乖合作,我就把你拆了
If he fix. Ed ya once, he can fix. Ya again. Now get in the box!
他一样能把你补好,给我进去
- Never! - Fine!
- 不要 - 好吧
- No! - Gotcha!
- 不 - 逮到你了
Idiots! Children destroy toys!
白痴,小孩子会毁了玩具
You'll all be ruined, forgotten!
你们会被玩坏、遗忘
Spending eternity rotting in some landfill!
永远被埋在垃圾场
Well, Stinky Pete, I think it's time you learned the true meaning of playtime.
邋遢彼得,你该学会怎么跟小孩玩了
- Right over there, guys! - No. No! No!
- 把他放到那儿 - 不!不!
Atlantic Air flight 810 from Point Richmond
大西洋航空810号班机
now arriving at Gate 3.
抵达三号登机门
Look, Barbie. A big ugly man doll.
芭比,你看,好丑的老娃娃
(芭比)
He needs a makeover.
我要帮他整容
Hi! You'll like Amy.
嗨,你会喜欢艾美
She's an artist!
她是天才艺术家
Come on, hon!
走吧,乖乖
Happy trails, Prospector.
祝你幸福,老矿工
- Buzz! Woody! - Help us out here!
- 巴斯、胡迪 - 帮帮忙
Hurry!
快点
- Oh, no. Jessie! Come on! - Woody!
- 糟了,翠丝,快点 - 救命啊
Jessie!
翠丝
Come on, Buzz.
巴斯,上来吧
Ride like the wind, Bullseye!
快马加鞭吧,红心
Hey-howdy-hey! Giddyap!
快点,马儿
Come on, Bullseye!
跑快点,红心
Buzz, give me a boost!
巴斯,把我抬起来
Woody!
胡迪
(远东航空)
Here's the rest!
只剩下这些了
Ex. Cuse me, ma'am, but I believe you're on the wrong flight.
抱歉,小姐,你搭错班机了
- Woody! - Come on, jess.
- 胡迪 - 来吧,翠丝
It's time to take you home.
我带你回家
- But what if Andy doesn't like me? - Nonsense! Andy'll love you!
- 要是安弟不喜欢我怎么办? - 别傻了,他会喜欢你
- Besides, he's got a little sister. - He does?
- 而且他有个小妹妹 - 真的吗?
Why didn't you say so? Let's go!
你怎么不早说?快走吧
Hold it! There's a couple more bags coming from the terminal!
等等,还有几件行李没到
OK. On three.
我数到三
- One, two... - Too late!
- 一、二… - 太迟了
Put 'em on the next flight!
等下一班机吧
- This is bad. - How are we gonna get outta here?
- 这下可糟了 - 我们该怎么出去?
Over there! Come on!
这儿,来吧
- You sure about this? - No! Let's go!
- 你确定吗? - 不!来吧!
(调准水平)
Hold on, Woody!
抓紧了,胡迪
- What's a cowboy without his hat? - Buzz!
- 牛仔没有牛仔帽怎么行? - 巴斯
Buzz! Buzz, get behind the tires!
巴斯,到轮胎后面
Jessie, let go of the plane!
翠丝,放手
What? Are you crazy?
你疯啦?
Just pretend it's the final episode of Woody's Roundup.
假装这是“胡迪牛仔秀”大结局
But it was canceled! We never saw if you made it!
它被停播了,你不知道结局
Well, then, let's find out together!
我们现在一起演吧
We did it! We did it! We did it!
成功了!成功了!
Nice ropin', cowboy.
干得好,牛仔
That was definitely Woody's finest hour!
这是胡迪最光荣的一刻
Your hat, partner.
你的帽子,伙伴
Let's... go home.
咱们回家吧
Hey, Woody! Woody?
胡迪,胡迪?
(安弟,欢迎回家)
Wow! New toys!
新玩具,酷毙了
Cool! Thanks, Mom!
谢了,妈咪
It's Bazooka jane and her jet-propelled horse!
火箭炮珍妮和她的喷射马
Woody, Buzz, that polecat Zurg has stolen my space cows
胡迪、巴斯,札克偷走我的太空牛
and they're headed for the asteroid!
他们飞到陨石带了
Andy, come on, hon. Time to go.
安弟,该走了
- Hey, you fix. Ed Woody! - Yeah.
- 你把胡迪补好了 - 是啊
Glad I decided not to take him to camp. His whole arm might have come off.
幸好我没带他去牛仔营,要不然他整只手都会被扯断
Well, what do you know?
真没想到
Bullseye, we're part of a family again!
红心,我们又有新的家了
(弟安)
(安弟)
Ma'am, I...
小姐,我想告诉你
I wanted to say you're a bright young woman
你是个毛线飘逸的…
with a beautiful "yarnful" of hair.
…漂亮姑娘
"Hairful" of yarn. It's...
我是说秀发飘逸
I must go.
我得走了
Well, aren't you the sweetest space toy I ever met?
你是我见过,最可爱的太空玩具
What's that? Bark-bark?
什么事?
This fella says he needs to go out for a little private time.
小狗狗得到后院方便一下
That critter needs help!
那只狗需要帮忙
Rex, I could use a hand over here, buddy.
抱抱龙,帮帮忙
I don't need to play. I've lived it!
我不必玩了,我亲手打败过札克
Oh, nuts!
惨了惨了,可恶
Welcome to Al's Toy Barn.
欢迎光临艾而玩具城
We've got the lowest prices in town.
我们的价格最便宜
Everything for a buck-buck-buck.
每样玩具都一块钱
Well, I guess crime doesn't pay.
犯罪没有好下场
Andy did a great job, huh? Nice and strong!
安弟把我缝得好结实
I like it. Makes you look... tough.
我喜欢,你很强壮
You have saved our lives. We are eternally grateful.
你救了我们,我们永远感谢你
You saved their lives? My hero!
你救了他们?喔,我的英雄
And they're so adorable! Let's adopt them!
他们好可爱,我们领养他们吧
Daddy!
爸爸
Oh, no.
不要吧
Wheezy, you're fix. Ed!
吱吱,你被修好了
Oh, yeah. Mr. Shark looked in the toy box. And found me an extra squeaker.
是啊,鲨鱼先生找到一个吱吱盒
- And... how do you feel? - I feel swell.
- 你觉得怎样? - 好得不得了
In fact, I think I feel a song comin' on.
我想要为大家献唱一曲
You've got a friend in me
我是你好朋友
You just remember what your old pal said
紧紧记住这句话
Babe you've got a friend in me
我是你好朋友
Yeah you've got a friend in me
Come on over. You are such a big girl.
妹妹,你越长越高啰
Andy, you think she's ready to drive the car yet?
你看她可以开车了吗?
Yeah, and I can teach her.
可以啊,我来教她
- You still worried? - About Andy?
- 你还在担心? - 担心安弟?
- No, it'll be fun while it lasts. - I'm proud of you, cowboy.
- 才不,好时光要珍惜 - 我以你为傲,牛仔
Besides, when it all ends, I'll have old Buzz Lightyear to keep me company...
就算安弟长大了,巴斯光年还是我的好朋友
...for infinity and beyond.
一同飞向宇宙…直到永远
You're gonna see it's our destiny
这是上天注定的命运
- You've got a friend in me - Yes you do
- 我是你好朋友 - 一点也没错
- You've got a friend in me - That's the truth
- 我是你好朋友 - 说得好
You've got a friend
我是你…
In me
…好朋友
(吱吱)
Yeah!
好耶